This is much better.
Much better than the last
competition's photos.
Yeah, we have to rely on ourselves.
Look at
Fu Binyan's photo.
He could start his career with that.
It's Xu Anbo who took a good photo.
It has nothing to do with me.
There are many more photos.
I'll upload them to the cloud
and send you the link.
Okay.
Chen Song,
haven't you joined the group yet?
I'll add you.
I'm not on the basketball team.
Chen Song,
we've fought side by side.
From now on, we're family.
Yeah, yeah.
You're officially an honorary member.
Thank you so much.
Louder!
It's all because of you
that yesterday's performance
was such a success.
Don't say that.
Without your script
and the quota for performance,
we can't stand on
the stage of the Arts Festival.
That's right.
How about writing
a story
about our Basketball Club next time?
Okay.
I'm just thinking about it.
The photos are good.
Thank you.
The number of people in this group
is not right.
Fu Binyan,
are you not in the group?
I didn't join the Basketball Club.
I thought you
were very close to them.
I'll add you to the group.
I'll take a call.
OK.
You go ahead.
Is he
unhappy?
It's okay.
That's his character.
You'll know it later.
What's that saying?
He is not as cold as he looks.
He is a warm person inside.
You're my savior.
By the way,
when can he officially
join the basketball club?
Director
This is the work report
of the Arts Festival.
The winning team's prize money and certificates
will be in place this week.
Our basketball team
is really something.
But this time, the response was great.
My
biggest concern
finally did something right.
Have you been keeping an eye on them lately?
Everything's been
on track.
They've been training diligently every day.
No issues at all.
Good.
But...
What? Just say it.
They represent the school's honor,
giving it their all.
At the Arts Festival,
they achieved the best results.
They're too excellent
to continue being your
biggest headache.
Alright, I got it.
Anything else?
Director, I'll go now.
Okay, go ahead.
Fu Binyan, something is wrong with you.
You criticize us,
dislike us,
and never want to join us.
But you help us,
supervise us,
and even spoke well of us
behind our backs.
You have a problem.
I specifically inquired about you.
They said you like playing basketball very much,
and you are very good at it.
Your current
contradictory behavior
all point to one possibility.
And I
have already guessed it.
What?
You don't join the Basketball Club
because you
look down on us from the bottom of your heart.
Do you think
we are not good enough for you?
You want us to grow first.
When we are strong enough one day,
you will join us.
Yes, that's it.
So, for the next group match,
you all have to work hard.
Don't worry,
we will.
Keep going, keep going.
The coach lets us relax a bit.
But aren't we
a bit too relaxed like this?
It's okay.
Having fun
can bring out the best in us.
Come on,
guys, keep going.
Okay.
Fu Binyan,
do you want to join us?
Who let you play like this?
Coach,
how could you not include me?
Keep throwing,
smash those balls down for me.
Yes!
Good news!
What's the good news?
The Arts Festival awards
and the prize money have arrived!
We've got funding again!
That's great!
Now, everything's in place.
Our next game,
Yibei will win!
I can smell it
from afar.
What is it?
The smell of defeat.
Alright, stop dawdling.
Reflect and review.
Who
made the biggest mistake today?
Don't look around. It's you, Lin Qingyuan.
You insisted on shooting at a critical moment,
wasting many opportunities to turn the tables.
Li Haoyu,
you made many mistakes and fouls.
You are too hasty.
Zhou Yang, are you so tired?
You are not active enough.
Gu Chenyang, you are the same.
The more behind you are, the more you think.
You are hesitant to shoot.
Xu Anbo.
Where's Xu Anbo?
He had something at the boxing gym.
He and Chi Jia left early.
Look.
Running away after losing a game.
What kind of team is this?
Coach.
Today...
It wasn't that bad.
Yeah.
I didn't do well today,
but others
did well.
Coach,
Fanghe No. 3 Middle School is indeed strong.
We lost today
and made many mistakes,
but I think
our performance
wasn't that bad.
Yeah, coach.
Yeah.
Do you think so?
That's right.
Why do you
look so upset?
Why the long faces?
Winning and losing are common in games.
Fanghe No.3 Middle School
is the team
that fouls the most.
You guys were obviously
disturbed today.
But none of you
were injured.
That should be
the most gratifying thing.
So,
cheer up.
The game isn't over yet.
Let's
keep working hard.
Good, you all know how to answer quickly.
Okay.
Go home early.
Goodbye, coach.
As your supervisor,
I need to remind you
of something.
What?
Check the group chat.
According to the latest
club management rules,
if a club member fails
two or more exams,
or
ranks in the bottom
10%,
they'll be forced to
pause club activities for a month.
I've checked.
Lin Qingyuan, Li Haoyu,
your scores in the last two monthly exams
were both in the bottom 10% of your grade.
To be exact,
the bottom 5%.
That means
if they don't improve
in this midterm,
they won't be able to participate
in the following group matches.
What do you think?
What should we do?
Who can help us?
For the first function problem,
you can first look at
the AI's approach to solving it.
It's explained very clearly.
What's wrong?
Take a look for yourself.
Why are there so many words?
I didn't ask it to give you the answer,
but to use
Socratic method.
Starting from the question,
it guides you step by step
to analyze the problem, retrieve knowledge,
and solve the problem.
In this way,
you will not only learn
this question,
but you can handle
the whole type of questions.
This is called teaching a man to fish
instead of giving him a fish.
Orcs
are never slaves, right?
You just mentioned
Socrates.
Which game's hero
is he?
Ten minutes.
After watching,
I'll give you a similar question.
If you can't solve it,
you'll be penalized with five more.
Mr. Gu,
we have a question.
When is Mr. Zhou Yang coming?
Hello, Director Qian.
Hello.
Professor Lin,
thank you for coming today.
Your lecture on the Reading Week
was truly fantastic.
Director Qian, you're too kind.
This is mainly due to the national advocacy
and the school's support.
The Parent Committee
just played a small role.
Professor Lin,
you're too modest.
This year, we're just trying it out on our own.
Next year, for the National Reading Week,
Professor Lin,
we'll need your continued support.
I'll do my best to support it.
Thank you, thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello, Director Qian.
This young man,
are you from the Basketball Club?
Yes, ma'am. And who might you be?
Let me introduce.
This is
Gu Chenyang's mother,
Professor Lin Ruoyun.
Hello.
Hello, ma'am.
He's the president
of our Yibei Student Union,
Zhou...
Zhou Yang.
[Zhou Yang,]
[you finally]
[found us!]
[Zhou Yang, help us!]
What's going on?
Don't let Gu Chenyang
tutor us!
We're too far apart in intelligence.
It's like we're torturing each other!
Director.
Aunt Lin.
Long time no see, Haoyu.
Aunt, don't give it to him.
He can't even understand it.
You give it to him.
I can understand it.
Who says I can't?
Can you understand this?
Of course I can.
They're so lively.
This book, The Old Man and the Sea,
is for you.
Mom.
Thank you, auntie.
I know you like it.
Chen Yang is here.
He's here.
Come here.
Come and sit.
I'm giving out books to everyone.
Today at your school,
there was a promotion
of Reading Week.
Reading Week?
Yes, after the midterms,
the school will fully implement it.
From now on, everyone must read a book
in the first week of every month
and complete a reading report.
Why are there
so many tasks from the school?
It's hard to be a student,
and it's even harder to be
a good student.
With your grades,
do you really think you're good students?
Chen Yang,
everyone has their strengths.
Good students can be
defined in different ways.
Look at Xiaolin and Haoyu,
one is enthusiastic,
the other is loyal.
They're both good students, right?
Right.
But, you still need to study.
In our family,
Chenyang reads
two books a month.
He's been doing this for years.
Who would've thought?
That's the gap
between people.
Zhou Yang,
do you remember
our agreement?
I remember.
I'll help you catch up next week
and lighten Gu Chenyang's load.
Alright,
enough about studying.
Today, I'm treating.
Whoever eats the most
and enjoys the most
will be my
favorite student.
Okay?
Okay!
Let's eat!
Son, have some fruit.
What are you reading?
The Alchemist.
Why did you choose this one?
It's the first book
on the Reading Week recommendation list.
I want to finish
all the books this semester.
I thought
you were interested
in its content.
The content
is also quite good.
Santiago, the shepherd boy,
crossed the entire continent
to find the treasure.
On the way to pursuing his destiny,
he learned to use all resources,
persevered,
and finally realized their own value.
Are you going to
read all the books on the list like this?
You'll find life in the desert,
stars in the sky,
and soldiers fighting
because war
is part of human life.
Life is a festival,
a grand celebration.
Because life is
and will always be
the moment we are experiencing right now.
Don't remember, do you?
This is from the book.
I've long noticed that
for you, reading
is just about completing the tasks
your dad assigns to you.
If we use travel as a metaphor,
you are the type who sleeps on the bus
and checks in upon arrival,
and complete tasks
with the help of AI.
But real reading
isn't like that.
You need to
explore a whole new world,
feel the wind and rain,
and encounter all sorts of the unknown.
Mom,
I'm sorry.
You don't need
to apologize to me
for anything.
I know
your dad has always taught you
to be efficient.
But I
still hope you can slow down,
read a book,
and take the time
to appreciate life.
Maybe
you'll be happier that way.
Smile.
Here,
have an orange.
I won't bother you.
Take your time.
Okay.
Nice addition of an auxiliary line.
Can you share
how you thought of it?
Zhou Yang came up with it.
We discussed solutions yesterday.
Very good.
I'm looking forward
to your good news in the next month's competition.
Okay.
Go back.
That's it for today's training.
Class dismissed.
Auxiliary line?
Who doesn't know that?
Someone who doesn't even attend the training
wants to win an award?
That's funny.
Joining the training
is voluntary.
I came here
because I lack confidence.
I didn't expect
the level here to be even lower.
Fu Binyan.
Where's Zhou Yang?
He didn't come today.
What's up?
Is it about
the Reading Week?
Did he go
tutor Li Haoyu
and the others?
I'll talk to
Ms. Wang again.
As for Zhou Yang,
I'll leave it to you to remind him.
Okay.
[The spotlight burns the center of the]
[basketball court into a dazzling island.]
[The deafening roar]
[turns into a thick silence at this moment.]
[I stand on the free-throw line,]
[the white line beneath my feet]
[like a measure of fate.]
Not bad, bro. A literary genius.
Just a piece of cake.
Gu Chenyang,
what's the topic
of this essay?
With the theme of facing,
choose a familiar angle
to write a heartfelt essay.
Keep reading.
We're about to face it.
The score is tied.
Time is running out.
The team's hope
is on me,
a 17-year-old defender.
You're 17?
AI wrote this, right?
I just copied it.
Who said this is AI?
"A snow-bright island,
a sticky silence,
and the measure of fate."
That's your writing style.
I've known you for years.
Who are you looking down on?
Besides,
don't you use AI
every day?
I use AI
as a learning tool,
not to do my work for me.
Besides,
during exams,
can AI help you?
Enough, enough.
Let's check mine out.
Speaking of facing,
Lu Xun once said,
a true hero
dares to face a bleak life
and the bloodshed.
Franklin Roosevelt said,
face the things you fear
and go forward.
Charles de Gaulle said...
Bi Shumin said...
Einstein also said...
What's this?
Just tell me if it's correct
and on topic.
Are you using the composition paper
as a school corridor?
It's all quotes from famous people.
I don't have AI.
I searched for these quotes myself
and copied them by hand.
Can you copy during exams?
When writing essays,
the most important thing is genuine feelings.
AI may have a fancy way with words,
but it's too hollow.
Famous quotes
may make sense,
but they can't replace
our true feelings.
You two, rewrite an essay now.
About the last basketball game loss.
No, no.
We've lost the game.
Why do we have to write it?
This is called facing.
Do you understand?
Okay, okay.
Let's think about it.
All right.
I'll go buy you something to eat.
Come on.
Hello, mom.
I didn't go out with my classmates.
I was reading in the classroom.
I'll be back soon.
Bin Yan
Why are you here?
The Olympiad mathematics contest is coming.
You still have time to set up a study group.
It's okay.
I've arranged my time.
It won't delay the contest.
You have limited energy.
You may have made a schedule,
but can your body
handle it?
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
Why hasn't Zhou Yang come back?
Do you need help?
No, thanks.
You also need to
prepare for the Olympiad.
Well.
It's the business of Basketball Club.
We can handle it ourselves.
Go back early.
I'm going in.
Bye.
I'm back.
Why are you just back?
What did you buy?